A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial Press Office, Series 4 FA457
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Gubernatorial Press Office, 1966, 1969-1973; 4; 13.2 Cubic Feet 11 record storage cartons.
  - Robert A. (Bob) Wands Photos
    - Contact Prints
      - 1973
        - 1973 January
          - 1973 January 3 (Box 102)
          - 1973 January 7 (Box 102)
          - 1973 January 12 (Box 102)
          - 1973 January 17 (Box 102)
          - 1973 January 28 (Box 102)
          - 1973 January 29 (Box 102)
        - 1973 March
          - 1973 March 8 (Box 102)
          - 1973 March 9 (Box 102)
          - 1973 March 16 (Box 102)
        - 1973 April
          - 1973 April 5 (Box 102)
          - 1973 Aprl 11 (Box 102)
        - 1973 May
          - 1973 May 9 (Box 102)
  - Miscellaneous People and Subjects, 1970 August
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller with F. Adams (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Animals (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Arts & Entertainment (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Barbers (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller with African-Americans (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Cardinal Cooke (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Children (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Crowds (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller with John de Lury (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller discussing Drug and Health Problems (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller eating (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller at Endorsements (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Hard Hats (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller and Jewish Subjects (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller and L. Lefkowitz (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller and Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller with Sofia Loren (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Miss Universe (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller and WR at National Governors' Conference (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Political Figures (Box 103)
      - Attorney General (Box 103)
      - Senator Bridges (Box 103)
      - Speaker Durea (Box 103)
      - Proccacino (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Running Mates (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller giving Speeches (Box 103)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 103)
      - Tarrytown Centennial (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Sports Personalities (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Students (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Malcolm Wilson (Box 103)
      - Miscellaneous Photos of Nelson A. Rockefeller (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller and Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller (Box 103)
    - Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller - Portraits (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portraits - Formal (Box 103)
      - with glasses (Box 103)
      - without glasses (Box 103)
      - standing (Box 103)
      - color portraits (Box 103)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portraits - Informal (Box 103)
      - 3/4 shot with smile (Box 103)
      - at desk 55th St. (Box 103)
      - hand raised with smile (Box 103)
      - head-on, hair hanging (Box 103)
      - clapping hands (Box 103)
      - at Co-op City (Box 103)
      - by stream (Box 103)
      - with smile and striped shirt (Box 103)
      - speaking with "OK" sign (Box 103)
      - serious, speaking with glasses (Box 103)
    - Executive Mansion (Box 103)
    - Pocantico Rugs, 12/1/1971 (Box 103)
    - Mrs. Rockefeller, Jr. Apartment and MRB Funeral (Box 103)
    - Clippings and News Papers (Box 103)
    - Thank-you letters to Bob Wands (Box 103)
    - Photographs - Wide World Photos, 9-11/1966 (Box 122)
    - Photographs - Wide World Photos, 11/1966 (Box 123)
    - Photographs - Latin American Trip, 1969 (Box 123)
      Arrangement note
      Arranged by country.
    - Photographs - Miscellaneous and Undated (Box 124)
    - Photographs - Latin American Trip (Box 124)
    - Photographs - Miscellaneous and Undated (Box 125)
    - Photographs - Miscellaneous and Undated (Box 126)
    - Photographs - Miscellaneous, Oversized (Box 127)